mediavine.com 2019-06-12

# Privacy Policy - Mediavine

The following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) sets forth Mediavine, Inc.’s (“Mediavine”) policy with respect to information, including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) and other information, Mediavine collects from visitors to the Mediavine website located at [http://www.mediavine.com](https://www.mediavine.com/), including users of the Mediavine Direct platform located at [https://sales.mediavine.com](https://sales.mediavine.com/), the Mediavine Dashboard located at [https://dashboard.mediavine.com](https://dashboard.mediavine.com/) and the Mediavine Help Center located at [https://help.mediavine.com](https://help.mediavine.com/) (“you or “your) (collectively the “Sites”). The Sites are operated by Mediavine (“we” or “us”) and has been created to provide online advertising management services (together with the Sites, the “Services”).

## Information We Collect

When you interact with us through the Services, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below.

### Personal Data That You Provide Through the Services

We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you contact us with inquiries, register for access to the Services or use certain Services.

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to us, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred and stored from your current location to the offices and servers of Mediavine and the authorized third parties referenced below.

### Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information

Mediavine uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such Services and to monitor your use of such Services. Mediavine and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Related Companies”) may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Services, to better understand our users and to improve the Services. Mediavine and its affiliates may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as at privacy@mediavine.com.

If Mediavine intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.

## Other Information

### Non-Identifiable Data

When you interact with Mediavine through the Services, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Mediavine may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Mediavine affiliates, agents or service providers. The Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Sites, the number of visitors to each page of our Sites, and the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process.

The Sites may use cookies, web beacons or pixels. A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Services gives to your browser when you access the Services. The Sites use cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Site content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described below. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Services and help us analyze Services usage more accurately. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data without your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notifications when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. If you turn cookies off you may not be able to access some of the Services’ features.

Web beacons allow us to count the number of users who have visited or accessed the Sites and to recognize users by accessing our cookies. We may employ web beacons to facilitate Site administration and navigation, to track the actions of users of the Sites, to compile aggregate statistics about Site usage and response rates, and to provide an enhanced online experience for visitors to the Sites. We may also include web beacons in HTML-formatted e-mail messages that we send to determine which e-mail messages were opened.

### Aggregated Personal Data

In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, Mediavine often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Mediavine may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Mediavine may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

### Google Analytics

The Website uses Google Analytics to track statistics regarding our audience and Website traffic. No personally identifiable information is transferred from the Website to Google Analytics. [For more information on Google’s Analytics privacy policies, please visit this site.](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

From time to time, the website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the Website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Website. For more information about Google Ads, [check your Google Ad settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/authenticated).

**Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information**

Mediavine will not sell, distribute, or reveal users’ email addresses or other personal information, except when required by law, without their consent. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

### Business Transfers

As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets.

### Related Companies

We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties

Mediavine, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another entity to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.

### Legal Requirements

Mediavine may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Mediavine, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

**Third-Party Use of Personal Information**

The Site may provide personal information to an applicable third party in order to provide services. Currently, the Site uses the services of Stripe for payment processing. Stripe’s use of your personal information is subject to [Stripe’s privacy policy](https://stripe.com/us/privacy). The Site also uses Intercom for third-party communications. Intercom’s use of your personal information is subject to [Intercom’s privacy policy](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy).

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. If a new service provider is engaged, these terms will be amended accordingly. 

**Your Choices**

You can visit the Site without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, you may not be able to use certain Services. You may request deletion of your personal information by sending an email to privacy@mediavine.com, but in some cases, we may be required to keep your information by law. In such a case, it would no longer be active and would be kept separately in an archive.

**Exclusions**

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Mediavine other than Personal Data collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Mediavine through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Mediavine shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

**Children**

Mediavine does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Sites or the Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data on the Sites or Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Mediavine through the Sites or Services, please contact us immediately at privacy@mediavine.com, and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove that information from our databases.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Sites. The Sites may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by Mediavine (the “Third-Party Sites”). The policies and procedures described here do not apply to the Third-Party Sites. The links from the Services do not imply that Mediavine endorses or has reviewed the Third-Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

**Email Communications**

If you send us an email with questions or comments, we may use your personally identifiable information to respond to your questions or comments, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference. For security reasons, we do not recommend that you send non-public personal information, such as passwords, social security numbers, or bank account information, to us by email. You may “opt out” of receiving future commercial email communications from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link included at the bottom of most emails we send, or as provided below; provided, however, we reserve the right to send you transactional emails such as customer service communications.

**Other Terms and Conditions**

Your access to and use of the Site and Services may also be subject to any separate agreements or terms and conditions you have signed or agreed to with Mediavine. Please refer to those agreements as needed.

Regardless of any other provision in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable information about you to: (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law or legal process; (c) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Sites, or other users; or (d) protect, in an emergency, the health and safety of our customers or the general public. This includes exchanging information with third parties and organizations in connection with credit risk reduction and fraud protection.

**Changes to Mediavine’s Privacy Policy**

The Sites and Services may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Mediavine to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Mediavine reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

**Access to Information; Contacting Mediavine:**

To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Services. To unsubscribe from any communications, please contact us at the email address below.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about Mediavine’s Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Sites or Services.

You may contact us as follows: privacy@mediavine.com
